const QUESTION_U1 =
  [{id:'1usa1',
  rulelink:'1084672-rule-621-high-sticks',
  rulenum:'621d',//checked
    question: "The determining point at which a shot is determined to be a 'slap shot' in a Girls 10U league is when the back swing goes higher than the waist.",
    correctanswer:'True',
    incorrectanswers: [
      'False'
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa2',
  rulelink:'1062658-standard-of-play-casebook',
  rulenum:'Situation 5',//checked
    question: "Under the standard of play initiative, a defensive player in front of the net may use their strength and balance to gain an advantageous body position on the opponent. This is permitted so long as they do not use their arms or stick to create space between them and the opponent or use their stick to impede the opponent's ability to move in a desired direction.",
    correctanswer:'True',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa3',
  rulelink:'1084676-rule-625-interference',
  rulenum:'625a(9)',//checked
    question: "Any player on the players' or penalty bench who interferes, in any manner, with the movement of the puck on the ice while play is in progress, shall be assessed a minor penalty for_________?",
    correctanswer:'Interference',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "Unsportsmanlike Conduct",
      "Holding"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa4',
  rulelink:'1084713-rule-634-slashing',
  rulenum:'634d',//checked
    question: "An attacking player makes stick contact with the goalkeeper who has covered the puck and is in his/her crease. The whistle had not been blown yet. The proper action is:",
    correctanswer:'Assess the offending player a two minute minor penalty for slashing',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "Warn the player that he/she should not to do that again",
      "Give the goalkeeper a penalty for delay of game"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa5',
  rulelink:'1084660-rule-613-face-off-procedures',
  rulenum:'613c',//checked
    question: "After both teams have properly lined up for the face-off, the official conducting the face-off shall blow his/ her whistle to signal to both teams that he/she is about to drop the puck.",
    correctanswer:'False',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "True"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa6',
  rulelink:'1084675-rule-624-icing-the-puck',
  rulenum:'624c',//checked
    question: 'Please indicate the proper face-off location: Icing error by officials',
    correctanswer:"End Zone Face-off spot",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "Neutral Zone Face-off spot",
      "Center Ice Face-off spot"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa7',
  rulelink:'1084662-rule-614-falling-on-puck',
  rulenum:'614b',//checked
    question: "With one minute left in the game, Team A removes their goaltender. A defender from Team A then covers the puck in their goal crease in an attempt to prevent a goal. The official can award a goal",
    correctanswer:'True',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa8',
  rulelink:'1084477-rule-401-penalties',
  rulenum:'401b',//checked
    question: "During the course of a youth hockey game Team A receives 15 penalties. The coach responsible for the team at the time of the 15th penalty is immediately given a _______.",
    correctanswer:'Game suspension and is ejected for the remainder of that game',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "Bench minor and may stay on the bench for the remainder of that game",
      "Game misconduct and is ejected for the remainder of that game and the following game"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa9',
  rulelink:'1062658-standard-of-play-casebook',
  rulenum:'Situation 5', //checked
    question: "According to the Standard of Play and Rules Emphasis, two players are battling in front of the goal and competing for body position. The defensive player uses the stick, with no extension of the arms, to 'steer' the attacking player in a desired direction. May this be considered cross-checking?",
    correctanswer:'No, there is nothing illegal about this action',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "Yes, since the stick is exposed between the hands it must be enforced",
      "Yes, steering is the same as impeding so it must be a penalty"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa10',
  rulelink:'1084478-rule-402-minor-penalties',
  rulenum:'402b',//checked
    question: "All bench minor penalties must be served by a non-penalized player who was on the ice at the time of the infraction, except the goalkeeper.",
    correctanswer:'True',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa11',
  rulelink:'1084651-rule-607-charging',
  rulenum:'607d(Note1)',//checked
    question: "Team A's goalkeeper leaves his privileged area to play a puck in the corner of his defensive zone. A Team B player skates into the zone and delivers an avoidable check to the goalkeeper after the goalkeeper passed the puck up the boards. What penalty should the referee assess?",
    correctanswer:'A minor plus misconduct penalty for charging',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "No penalty shall be assessed. The goalkeeper is eligible to be checked in this situation",
      "A minor penalty for charging"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa12',
  rulelink:'1084982-delaying-the-game',
  rulenum:'Situation 1',//checked
    question: "The puck is along the side boards and players from both teams are actively trying to gain possession of the puck but the puck is surrounded by a player's skates. The correct call is:",
    correctanswer:'No whistle, allow play to continue',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "Whistle for a frozen puck",
      "Whistle if the puck does not move for four seconds"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa13',
  rulelink:'1084652-rule-608-checking-from-behind',
  rulenum:'608b',//checked
    question: "What is the minimum penalty that can be assessed to any player who body checks or pushes an opponent from behind causing them to go head first into the boards or goal frame?",
    correctanswer:'Major plus game misconduct',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "Minor penalty",
      "Minor plus misconduct."
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa14',
  rulelink:'1084351-composition-of-teams',
  rulenum:'Situation 2',//checked
    question: "Through injuries and penalties, a team becomes unable to place four players on the ice during the game. The game shall be declared a forfeit.",
    correctanswer:'True',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "False"
    ]
  },

  { id:'1usa15',
  rulelink:'1084571-calling-of-penalties',
  rulenum:'Situation 8', //checked
    question: "Team A is one minute into a power play, Team B commits another penalty and the referee has his/her hand up for a delayed call. Before the offending team can get possession and control of the puck, Team A scores",
    correctanswer:'The penalty currently being served is terminated and the new penalty is assessed and served',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "The player currently serving a penalty stays in the box, and the delayed penalty is terminated",
      "Both the penalty being served and the delayed penalty are terminated because of the goal"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa16',
  rulelink:'1015119-standard-of-play-and-rule-emphasis-body-checking',
  rulenum:'STANDARD OF PLAY & RULE EMPHASIS - BODY CHECKING', //checked
    question: "According to the Standard of Play and Rule Emphasis definition of body checking, which of the following is NOT a principle of this enforcement standard?",
    correctanswer:'The check may be delivered to any area above the shoulders if delivered directly from in front or the side of the opponent',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "The purpose of a body check is to separate the opponent from the puck",
      "Only the trunk (hips to shoulders) of the body shall be used to deliver a body check"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa17',
  rulelink:'1084645-rule-601-abuse-of-officials-and-other-misconduct',
  rulenum:'601d(3)', //checked
    question: "A player bangs the boards with their stick in protest of an official's decision against his/her team. The proper penalty assessment is",
    correctanswer:'A misconduct or game misconduct and an unsportsmanlike conduct minor.',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "A minor penalty for unsportsmanlike conduct",
      "A major and a game misconduct"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa18',
  rulelink:'1084666-rule-618-handling-puck-with-hands',
  rulenum:'618b',//checked
    question: "A hand pass initiated in the defensive zone may be completed in the neutral zone.",
    correctanswer:'False',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "True"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa19',
  rulelink:'1085038-off-sides',
  rulenum:'Situation 24',//checked
    question: "Team A, a 12U team, has possession and control of the puck in their defending zone. With a Team B player in Team A's defending zone, Team A attempts a pass that deflects off a Team A player in the neutral zone back into Team A's defending zone. The linesman shall signal a washout for a legal play.",
    correctanswer:'False',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "True"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa20',
  rulelink:'1084985-face-off-locations',
  rulenum:'Sutuation 1', //checked
    question: "At a stoppage of play in Team A's defensive zone the following penalties are assessed: #5 from Team A receives a minor penalty for roughing, #12 from Team B receives a minor for slashing and #21 from Team B receives a minor for roughing. Team B will play shorthanded for two minutes. Where is the ensuing face-off?",
    correctanswer:"Team A's defensive zone",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "Nearest neutral zone spot",
      "Team B's defensive zone"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa21',
  rulelink:'1084675-rule-624-icing-the-puck',
  rulenum:'624a(Note) & 409a',//checked
    question: "With a delayed penalty in effect, the non-offending team ices the puck. Where is the ensuing face-off located?",
    correctanswer:'At a neutral zone face-off spot outside the blue line of the team that iced the puck',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "At an end zone face-off spot of the penalized team",
      "At an end zone face-off spot of the team that iced the puck"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa22',
  rulelink:'1084718-rule-639-tripping-clipping-leg-checking',
  rulenum:'639b',//checked
    question: "The penalty options for injuring an opponent due to clipping are:",
    correctanswer:'Major plus game misconduct',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "Minor or major plus game misconduct",
      "Match penalty"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa23',
  rulelink:'1084645-rule-601-abuse-of-officials-and-other-misconduct',
  rulenum:'601e(5)',//checked
    question: "For the second misconduct assessed to the same player in the same game, a game misconduct penalty shall be assessed to that player in lieu of the second misconduct.",
    correctanswer:'True',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa24',
  rulelink:'1084688-rule-630-off-sides',
  rulenum:'630a',//checked
    question: "A player is offside when they do not have skate contact with any part of the neutral zone or the blue line when the puck crosses the determining edge of the blue line",
    correctanswer:'True',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa25',
  rulelink:'1084353-players-in-uniform',
  rulenum:'Situation 5',//checked
    question: "A player receives a penalty and is not listed on the scoresheet. The proper action to be taken by the officials is?",
    correctanswer:"Add the player's name to the scoresheet and assess the penalty as long as the maximum number of players is not already listed on the scoresheet, and assess a bench minor.",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "Only assess the penalty to the player",
      "Disallow the penalty and tell the player to leave the game"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa26',
  rulelink:'1084493-misconduct-penalties',
  rulenum:'Situation 5',//checked
    question: "A player has been assessed a second misconduct penalty in the same game. At the time the penalty is assessed, the penalty timekeeper fails to notify the referee that the player has just received his second misconduct in one game, requiring a game misconduct penalty. The situation is brought to the attention of the referee after a few minutes of play following the incident. What action should the referee take?",
    correctanswer:'After being informed, have the player removed from the game and have the scoresheet reflect the proper assessment.',
    incorrectanswers: ["After being informed at the next stoppage, assess a bench minor to the offending team and assess the game misconduct to the offending player",
      "Since the scorekeeper did not say anything the referee takes no action"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa27',
  rulelink:'1015130-zero-tolerance-policy',
  rulenum:'ZERO TOLERANCE POLICY-Officials',//checked
    question: "Officials are required to conduct themselves in a businesslike, sportsmanlike, impartial and constructive manner at all times.",
    correctanswer:'True',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa28',
  rulelink:'1084355-change-of-players',
  rulenum:'Situation 14', //checked
    question: "If a player on the penalty bench remains there after the expiration of their penalty (while his/her team is entitled to return to full strength), may his/her team place another skater on the ice as long as the originally penalized player remains on the penalty bench?",
    correctanswer:'No, the player on the penalty bench must be on the ice and at the bench before they can be substituted',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "Yes, but his/her team must have possession and control of the puck.",
      "Yes, once the time has expired anyone can join play"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa29',
  rulelink:'1084402-rule-304-protective-equipment',
  rulenum:'304c',//checked
    question: "It is mandatory that all players (except adults) wear a current (unexpired date) HECC-approved helmet with the chin strap securely fastened.",
    correctanswer:'True',
    incorrectanswers: [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa30',
  rulelink:'1089267-goal-scored',
  rulenum:'GOAL SCORED',//checked
    question: 'The proper signal for a goal scored is pointing at the goal with your non-whistle hand while simultaneously blowing the whistle',
    correctanswer:"True",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "False"
    ]
  },

  { id:'1usa31',
  rulelink:'1084657-rule-612-face-off-locations',
  rulenum:'612b',//checked
    question: 'All face offs during a hockey game will take place at one of the nine (9) designated face-off spots on the ice surface',
    correctanswer:"True",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa32',
  rulelink:'1084672-rule-621-high-sticks',
  rulenum:'621c',//checked
    question: 'Please indicate the proper face-off location: High Sticked puck',
    correctanswer:"End Zone Face-off",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "Neutral Zone Face-off spot",
      "Center Ice Face-off spot"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa33',
  rulelink:'1015129-codes-of-conduct',
  rulenum:"On-Ice Official's Code of Conduct", //checked
    question: 'An official should answer all reasonable questions and requests and should admit their mistakes when they make them',
    correctanswer:"True",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa34',
  rulelink:'1084405-rule-307-equipment-measurement',
  rulenum:"307a", //checked
    question: 'A team can request more than one equipment measurement per stoppage of play',
    correctanswer:"False",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "True"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa35',
  rulelink:'1084356-injured-players',
  rulenum:"Situation 1", //checked
    question: 'When should you stop play for an injured/hurt player',
    correctanswer:"Immediately if the injury appears to be serious",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "Immediately, even if the injury appears to be minor",
      "You must always wait until the injured player's team has possession of the puck"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa36',
  rulelink:'1062658-standard-of-play-casebook',
  rulenum:"Situation 2", //checked
    question: "According to USA Hockey's Standard of Play initiative, lifting an opponent's stick will always be a penalty",
    correctanswer:"False",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "True"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa37',
  rulelink:'1084665-rule-617-goals-and-assists',
  rulenum:"617c(4)", //checked
    question: 'A goal should be disallowed if an attacking player was in the goal crease when the puck entered the goal',
    correctanswer:"True",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa38',
  rulelink:'1062658-standard-of-play-casebook',
  rulenum:"Situation 3", //checked
    question: "Which of the following is an illigal play according to USA Hockey's Standard of Play Initiative",
    correctanswer:"Poking the glove of an opponent with the stick, preventing the player from being able to shoot the puck",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "Using the free arm to maintain their body position while carrying the puck",
      "Both options are illigal"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa39',
  rulelink:'1062658-standard-of-play-casebook',
  rulenum:"Situation 12", //checked
    question: "According to USA Hockey's Standard of Play Initiative, players are entitled to the ice they occupy as long as they are able to maintain their own foot speed and body position between the puck and opponent",
    correctanswer:"True",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa40',
  rulelink:'1084664-rule-616-fouled-from-behind',
  rulenum:"616a & BM 61", //checked
    question: "Which is NOT one of the five criteria that has to be met for a penalty shot to be awarded?",
    correctanswer:"The player is fouled from behind, diagonally from behind, or from the side",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "The player is deprived of a reasonable scoring opportunity",
      "There is no opponent present between the player and the opposing goalkeeper",
      "The player must be beyond his or her defending blue line (ie neutral and attacking zone)",
      "The player must be in possession and control of the puck"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa41',
  rulelink:'1084648-rule-604-body-checking',
  rulenum:'604b',//checked
    question: 'A boys 12 & Under team is playing a boys 14 & Under team. If both coaches agree:',
    correctanswer:"Even though the coaches have agreed otherwise, the game must use body contact rules.",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "The teams may check but only safely.", "The teams may use body checking in the game."
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa42',
  rulelink:'1084477-rule-401-penalties',
  rulenum:'401b',//checked
    question: 'A player in one game receives a minor penalty for tripping, a double minor for unnecessary roughness, and a minor and misconduct for charging. This player:',
    correctanswer:"Has five penalties and should be assessed a game misconduct penalty.",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "Should be told to behave.", "Only has four penalties."
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa43',
  rulelink:'1084654-rule-610-delaying-the-game',
  rulenum:'610d',//checked
    question: 'A minor penalty for delay of game shall be assessed to a goalkeeper who shoots the puck directly (non deflected) outside of the playing area, except when the puck inadvertently leaves the playing area in a location that is not protected by glass or screen: (example players bench).',
    correctanswer:"True",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa44',
  rulelink:'1084688-rule-630-off-sides',
  rulenum:'630e',//checked
    question: 'A linesman makes an obvious error in stopping play for a puck carried off-sides. The ensuing face-off shall take place at the Center Ice face-off spot',
    correctanswer:"False",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "True"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa45',
  rulelink:'1084485-rule-408-delayed-penalties',
  rulenum:'408b',//checked
    question: 'Three (3) players from the same team are on the penalty bench serving non-coincident minor penalties assessed at different times. When the first penalty expires, that player whose penalty expired may return to the ice immediately',
    correctanswer:"False",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "True"
    ]
  },

  { id:'1usa46',
  rulelink:'1084489-rule-411-progressive-suspensions',
  rulenum:'411b(Note)',//checked
    question: 'Officials are required to submit a game report immediately following the game for any major penalty falling in the aggressive infraction category, game misconduct or match penalty that is assessed',
    correctanswer:"True",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa47',
  rulelink:'1084645-rule-601-abuse-of-officials-and-other-misconduct',
  rulenum:'601e(3)', //checked
    question: 'In addition to a racial/ethnic slur, a match penalty can be assessed for any language that is deemed offensive, hateful ordiscriminatory in nature',
    correctanswer:"True",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa48',
  rulelink:'1084674-rule-623-hooking',
  rulenum:'623b',//checked
    question: 'A major plus a game misconduct penalty shall be assessed to any player who injures an opponent as a result of hooking',
    correctanswer:"True",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa49',
  rulelink:'1084718-rule-639-tripping-clipping-leg-checking',
  rulenum:'639',//checked
    question: 'Tripping, Clipping, Leg Checking and Slew Footing all carry the same penalty options, Minor or Major Penalty OR Major Penalty and Game Misconduct if an injury occurs',
    correctanswer:"True",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  { id:'1usa50',
  rulelink:'1084676-rule-625-interference',
  rulenum:'625b',//checked
    question: 'Please indicate the proper face-off location: Goal Crease Violation',
    correctanswer:"Neutral Zone Face-off ",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "End Zone Face-off spot",
      "Center Ice Face-off spot."
    ]
  }


];


export default QUESTION_U1;


//https://www.usahockeyrulebook.com/page/show/1084647-rule-603-boarding#pageEl_39686374
//https://www.usahockeyrulebook.com/page/show/1084647#pageEl_39686374
//https://www.usahockeyrulebook.com/page_element/ajax/34377950.json
